So hello everyone, these are the results of III Loam Board for the
second quarter. Let's see
how the results of this share have been.
We will start with the total income of this share. The
income here on yearly basis was
449,903, which has now become 0492
on quarterly basis, that is, the
income of the share has increased on quarterly basis. Let's
look at the total expenses of this share. The
expense of this share on yearly basis was 3988,182, which has now become 445,205 on quarterly basis.
Now let's
look at the profit after tax here, which was
5953, which has now become
577,227. Next, we will
also look at the dividend of this share, which was
earlier ₹100, which has now become
around ₹100, that is, overall
analysis.  After doing this, we can see that the
results here are good. The maximum target of the share till this month is around
₹1,500. So,
if you have this share
and you want to hold this share here, then
you can hold this share at your own risk from a long term
perspective.